# **MOHAMED SALAH**

### FLUTTER DEVEOLPER

mohamed\_salah\_414@yahoo.com

### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Always up for a challenge, I have worked for freelancers' sites and gotten more experience from companies and start-ups where I worked with. I have a **Bs.** in **Computer Science** and many years of experience in designing and marketing before going into **flutter** development. that helped me to improve in **UI/UX** design at the same time developing **flutter** apps.

#### **CONTACT DETAILS**

Mobile: 01203650266

E-mail: mohamed\_salah\_414@yahoo.com Website: https://mohamedsalah414.github.io/

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamedsalah414/ GitHub: https://github.com/mohamedsalah414 Dribbble: https://dribbble.com/mohamedsalah414

#### **FLUTTER SKILLS**

- Dart
- OOP Data Structure Algorithms
- MVVM pattern
- GetX Provider
- Dio Http
- RESTful API
- Firebase
- Push Notification
- Work with Adobe XD & Figma
- SQL lite
- Shared preferences
- Authentication system
- PayPal Payment Integration
- Google Maps
- Pusher Channel Chat
- Git (GitHub)
- Sound & Video integration

#### **EDUCATION**

Alexandria University
Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science
Sep 2016 - Jul 2021

### **LANGUAGUE**

- Arabic (Native)
- English (Very Good)

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Flutter developer
Coappso · Full-time

Mar 2022 – **Present** Alexandria, Egypt

• Mobile Application Developer

Freelance

Feb 2020 - Present

UI/UX Designer

Freelance

Jan 2021 - Present

### **FLUTTER PROJECTS**

**Entertainment App** 





**Delivery and Shipping** 



**Portfolio** 



Sample Portfolio for my work and contacts

## **Casting (Actor side)**

Each actor can browse and apply for each director's projects from films, advertisements, or filming sessions, and can view his own photos and videos, and create his own photo gallery, explaining his technical and personal specifications.

### Hera (Customer side)

Ladies can book appointments to go to the beauty center and browse the services and products and chat with the beauty center.

## **Gym System (User & Trainer sides)**

The user can book a training session in the gym with or without his personal trainer using the application's coins and can search across the map for the nearest branches, specify directions to them, browse the trainers' photos and videos, and message them and the gym as well.

# Clinic System (Patient side)

The patient can browse the clinics and doctors and book the appropriate appointment for him, and he can chat with the clinic.

# Hiring System (Company side)

Each company can create its own account that contains all its information and can search for employees to hire them based on some of the requirements specified by the company.

### Reminder Religious App

The application contains the Holy Qur'an without the Internet or ads and contains translation, interpretation, and reading in the voice of the sheikhs, and the user can activate the notifications for the call to prayer and remind him of some religious supplications.

#### **OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE**

- FOUNDER & INSTRUCTOR CS SCOPE
  - Mar 2019 Present
- Graphic Designer Freelancer Apr 2009 - Present
- Data Entry Alwaleed host Jul 2017 - Jan 2018
- Sales Marketing Alwaleed host Aug 2016 - Jan 2018

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Developed team leading skills through my role of team leader in Entertainment App project
- Developed team leading skills through my role of team leader, founder, and instructor in **CS SCOPE** project
- Multi-tasks handling.
- Dealing effectively with others through working on projects of academic courses.
- Problem solving.
- Time Management